(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
あわてんぼうのサンタクロース
The Hasty Santa Claus
あわてんぼうの
A hasty
サンタクロース
Santa Claus
クリスマスまえに
before Christmas
やってきた
came along.
いそいでリンリンリン
In a hurry, ring-ring-ring,
in a hurry, ring-ring-ring,
ならしておくれよ　かねを
go ahead and ring the bells!
リンリンリン　リンリンリン　リンリンリン
Ring-ring-ring, ring-ring-ring, ring-ring-ring!
あわてんぼうの
A hasty
サンタクロース
Santa Claus
えんとつのぞいて
peeked into the chimney
おっこちた
and fell right in!
あいたたドンドンドン
Ouch-ouch-ouch, bang-bang-bang,
ouch-ouch-ouch, bang-bang-bang,
まっくろくろけのおかお
with a face as black as soot!
ドンドンドン　ドンドンドン　ドンドンドン
Bang-bang-bang, bang-bang-bang, bang-bang-bang!
あわてんぼうの
A hasty
サンタクロース
Santa Claus
しかたがないから
since there was nothing else to do,
おどったよ
started to dance!
たのしくチャチャチャ
Merrily, cha-cha-cha,
merrily, cha-cha-cha,
みんな...
everyone...
…みんなもおどるよ　ぼくと
...everyone dance with me.
チャチャチャ　チャチャチャ　チャチャチャ
Cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha, cha-cha-cha!
あわてんぼうの　サンタクロース
The scatterbrained Santa Claus
もういちどくるよと　かえってく
Goes back, saying he'll come again
さよなら　シャラランラン
Goodbye, shararan-ran
タンブリンならしてきえた
Disappeared while playing the tambourine
シャラランラン　シャラランラン　シャラランラン
Shararan-ran, shararan-ran, shararan-ran
あわてんぼうの　サンタクロース
The scatterbrained Santa Claus
ゆかいなおひげの　おじいさん
The funny old man with the beard
リンリンリン　チャチャチャ　ドンドンドン　シャラランラン
Rin-rin-rin, cha-cha-cha, don-don-don, shararan-ran
わすれちゃだめだよ　おもちゃ
Don't forget the toys
リンリンリン　チャチャチャ　ドンシャララン
Rin-rin-rin, cha-cha-cha, don-shararan
ドンシャララン
Don-shararan!
わあ！はい！どうも！あわてんぼうのサンタクロースこと…
Waa! Yes! Hello! I'm the scatterbrained Santa Claus...
…白銀聖騎士団の団長、白銀ノエルでーす！
...Leader of the Shirogane Order of Knights, Shirogane Noel!
みんな、今日は何の日か知ってますか？
Everyone, do you know what day it is today?
ふんふんふん…そうだよね！めちゃめちゃ大切な日だよね！
Mm-hm, mm-hm... That's right! It's a very, very important day!
おうおうおう…そう、皆様ご存じの通り、クリスマスイブだよー！わーい！
Oh, oh, oh... Yes, as you all know, it's Christmas Eve! Yay!
え、今ね、個画面上で見てるみんなも、
And now, everyone watching on your individual screens,
クリスマスライブの様子たくさん声でね、スクショしてSNSで投下してください。
please take lots of screenshots of the Christmas Live and post them on social media.
よろしくお願いします！これね、ハッシュタグはこちらとなっております。
Thank you! The hashtags are right here.
みんな、いっぱいスクショちょうだいね！
Everyone, please give me lots of screenshots!
そして、あの、今回クリスマスライブということで、ステージもクリスマス仕様となっております。わあすごい！
And, since this is a Christmas Live, the stage is also in a Christmas theme! Wow, amazing!
あの、いつもね、団長こう前に王宮の感じ作ってもらったんですけど…
Well, they usually make a royal palace feel for me...
その、街並みが、え、なんかパワーアップしてクリスマス仕様となってます。
...but the townscape has powered up and become Christmas-themed.
いや、すごいですね！煙突とかもね、すごかったですね！わーってなってますけれど。
Wow, it's incredible! The chimneys and all were great too! It's like "Whoa!"
いや、他にもちょっといろいろと見てみたいな…見れるのかな？
I want to see some other things too... Can I see them?
あ！プレゼント！やっぱクリスマスと言ったらプレゼントですよね！
Ah! Presents! When you think of Christmas, you think of presents, right?
いやいっぱい、ありがとうございます！きっとこれは団員さんからの愛かな？ありがとうございます！
Wow, there are so many! Thank you! I guess this is love from the Knights? Thank you very much!
そしてやっぱ他にもね、クリスマスと言ったら…（ドラムロール）…上のこちら！はい！リースもあります！
And of course, there's more to Christmas... (drumroll)... this thing up here! Yes! There's a wreath too!
なんかね、団長こうクリスマスと言ったらやっぱリースかなって思ったんですけど…
You know, when I think of Christmas, I think of wreaths...
ま、でもここらへんね、ちょっと気づいた方もいると思います。
...well, I think some of you might have noticed it around here.
いやー…あとなんだろうな？街並みとかね、プレゼント、リース、でサンタさんでしょう？
Hmm... what else? The townscape, presents, wreaths, and then Santa, right?
あ！一番大切ですね！こちら！そう！クリスマスツリー！
Ah! The most important one! This! Yes! The Christmas tree!
やっぱね、クリスマスツリーはクリスマスに欠かせませんけど…
You can't have Christmas without a Christmas tree, but...
え、どうやってライトアップする？やっぱさ、この何だろうね？
Um, how do we light it up? I mean, even if the tree is decorated...
ただなんかこう木が装飾してても、やっぱキラキラ光らないとクリスマスじゃない！どうしようどうしようどうしよう！
If the tree doesn't sparkle, it's just not Christmas! What should I do, what should I do, what should I do!
え、どうしようかなあ…悩む。
Hmm, what should I do... I'm stumped.
待って！わあ！あ！団員さん！あ、今動いてる！きゃー！
Wait! Whoa! Ah! A Knight! Oh, it's moving! Kyaa!
え、なんかこんなに動けたっけ団員さん？よかったね、ぴょんぴょんして。え、何なに？
Wait, could the Knights move this much? That's nice, you're hopping around. Eh, what is it?
あ、さっきね、そり、あの、大変だった？うんうん。でも引いてくれてありがとう！
Ah, was the sleigh hard work earlier? Mm-hm. But thanks for pulling it!
いやカッコいいよ！トナカイの角も似合ってます。かわいい！
Wow, you look cool! The reindeer antlers suit you too. Cute!
いや、クリスマス楽しんでますね！ということでね、
Wow, enjoying Christmas, aren't we! So,
本日、ま、クリスマスライブ、まだ成功したわけではありません。
...today's Christmas Live hasn't been a success just yet.
そう、最後まで成功するか分からない。なんと団員さんの力も必要です！
Right, I don't know if it'll be a success until the very end. I'll need the Knights' help too!
団員さんの応援、そして頑張りも、あのクリスマスライブの成功…何だろう、鍵になっておりますので、
Your support and hard work, dear Knights, are the key to the success of this Christmas Live.
ぜひぜひ応援よろしくお願いします！ではクリスマスの準備もしつつライブを楽しんでいきましょう！
So please, please support us! Now, let's enjoy the live while preparing for Christmas!
いやでもクリスマスね、一人で…ま、団員さんもいるけど、一人でなんかやる…
But you know, for Christmas, doing something alone... well, I have the Knights, but doing something alone...
一人はちょっと寂しいのでお友達も呼んでます。
It's a bit lonely by myself, so I'm calling my friends too.
お友達とクリスマスライブ歌って踊るぞー！
I'm going to sing and dance at a Christmas live with my friends!
わーい！ 楽しむぞー！
Yay! Let's have fun!
Ah ホイップしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the city is like a whipped cake
好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real magic
空がくれる コンフェッティは
The confetti the sky gives us
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ Woo
Are angel wings celebrating the winter festa Woo
Woo
白銀の国へ 出かけよう Go Go Go
Let's head to the silver country Go Go Go
雪の汽車が 街を駆け Choo Choo Choo
The snow train runs through the town Choo Choo Choo
絵本みたいな景色を 君に見せてあげるから
I'll show you a scenery like a picture book
願い込めて 呪文さあ
Put your heart into the spell, now
さあ！ 唱えて！ さんはい！
Now! Recite it! One, two!
A B C D ド ド シ シ ラ ラ シ シ マジカル ミラクル クルクル ポップ
A B C D do do si si la la si si magical miracle round and round pop
Ah ホイップしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the city is like a whipped cake
好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real magic
空がくれる コンフェッティは
The confetti the sky gives us
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
Are angel wings celebrating the winter festa
Light up したオーロラ色の街は
The aurora-colored city lit up
好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real magic
子供でいられたら Dream Land
If we could stay children, it's Dream Land
Dream Land
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to Snow Miku!
ツンと冷たい 季節が好き Love love love
I like the stinging cold season Love love love
アイスも魔法も 溶けないように ヒュー ヒュー ヒュー
So neither ice nor magic melt, whew whew whew
ずっとこのままじゃダメなの？
Is it no good to stay like this forever?
やっぱりドキドキしたいな
I really want to feel my heart race
未来求め 呪文今
Seeking the future, the spell is now
Now! 唱えて！ さんはい！
Now! Recite it! One, two!
1 2 3 4 水 金 地 火 木 マジカル ミラクル クルクル ポップ
1 2 3 4 Mercury Venus Earth Mars Jupiter magical miracle round and round pop
Ah ホップしたウサギのような気分
Ah, feeling like a hopping rabbit
好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real magic
大地がくれる 勇気得たら
If I get the courage the earth gives me
思い通り明日を 生きていけるよ
I can live tomorrow as I wish
まぶしい白に 染まるハート
A heart dyed in dazzling white
君に 好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
For you, love! snow! real magic
大人振るなんていいじゃん
It's okay to act like an adult
I hear that beat from town, the cute angel will come down
This is my home I'll let you know, Namara Fantastic
Snowflakes are lyrical, the street gonna be magical
I set you free in my land, Oh oh oh
今日の寒さも 忘れるように
So we can forget today's cold
悩みだって 凍らせて消せる魔法よ
It's magic that can freeze and erase worries
A B C D ド ド シ シ ラ ラ シ シ マジカル ミラクル クルクル ポップ
A B C D do do si si la la si si magical miracle round and round pop
Ah ホイップしたケーキのような街は
Ah, the city is like a whipped cake
好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real magic
空がくれる コンフェッティは
The confetti the sky gives us
冬のフェスタ祝う天使の羽よ
Are angel wings celebrating the winter festa
Light up したオーロラ色の街は
The aurora-colored city lit up
好き！ 雪！ 本気マジック
Love! Snow! Real magic
子供でいられたら Dream Land
If we could stay children, it's Dream Land
Dream Land
いいじゃん
It's good
はじめてのキスは涙の味がした
The first kiss tasted like tears
まるでドラマみたいな恋
A love just like a drama
見計らったように発車のベルが鳴った
The departure bell rang as if on cue
冷たい冬の風が頬をかすめる
The cold winter wind brushes my cheek
吐いた息で両手をこすった
I rubbed my hands together with my breath
街はイルミネーション 魔法をかけたみたい
The town is lit up, like a spell was cast
裸の街路樹キラキラ
The bare roadside trees are sparkling
どうしても言えなかった この気持ち 抑えつけた
I couldn't say it no matter what, I suppressed these feelings
前から決めていた事だから これでいいの
Because I had decided this long ago, this is fine.
振り向かないから
Because I won't look back.
ありがとう サヨナラ 切ない片想い
Thank you, goodbye, painful unrequited love.
足を止めたら思い出してしまう だから
If I stop walking, I'll end up remembering, so...
ありがとう サヨナラ 泣いたりしないから
Thank you, goodbye, because I won't cry.
そう思った途端に ふわり
Just as I thought that, softly...
舞い降りてくる雪 触れたら溶けて消えた
The falling snow, when touched, it melted and vanished.
駅へと続く大通り 寄り添ってる二人
On the main street leading to the station, a couple huddles together.
「ほら見て 初雪」
"Look, the first snow."
キミとあんな風になりたくて
I wanted to be like that with you.
初めて作った手編みのマフラー
The first hand-knitted muffler I ever made.
どうしたら渡せたんだろう 意気地なし 怖かっただけ
How could I have given it to you? No courage, I was just scared.
思い出になるなら このままで構わないって
If it's to become a memory, I don't mind staying like this.
それは本当なの？
Is that really true?
ありがとう サヨナラ いつかこんな時が来てしまうこと
Thank you, goodbye, that a time like this would come one day...
わかってたはずだわ なのに
I should have known, and yet...
ありがとう サヨナラ 体が震えてる
Thank you, goodbye, my body is shaking.
もうすぐ列車が来るのに
Even though the train is coming soon.
それは今になって 私を苦しめる
That now makes me suffer.
繋がりたい どれほど願っただろう
I want to be connected, how much I wished for it.
この手は空っぽ
These hands are empty.
ねえ サヨナラってこういうこと？
Hey, is this what "goodbye" means?
行かなくちゃ そんなのわかってる
I have to go, I know that.
キミが優しい事も知ってる だから
I know you're kind, so...
行かなくちゃ そんなのわかってる
I have to go, I know that.
キミが優しい事も知ってる だから
I know you're kind, so...
「この手を離してよ」
"Let go of this hand."
出会えてよかった キミが好き
I'm glad we met, I love you.
ありがとう サヨナラ 言葉が言えない
Thank you, goodbye, I can't say a word.
今だけでいい 私に勇気を
Just for now is fine, give me courage.
あのね 言いかけた唇 キミとの距離は０
You see... the lips that were about to speak, the distance to you is zero.
今だけは泣いていいよね
It's okay to cry just for now, right?
もう言葉はいらない お願いぎゅっとしていて
I don't need words anymore. Please, hold me tight.
...
来年の今頃には
Around this time next year,
どんな私が居て
what kind of person will I be,
どんなキミがいるのかな
and what kind of person will you be?
先輩！
Senpai!
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
イエーイ！すごーい！
Yay! Amazing!
なんか出たよ！クラッカー！
Something came out! Crackers!
クラッカーはい、用意してきました！
Crackers, yes, we prepared them!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
あわじゃあわじゃ...
(Flustered noises)
今回はクリスマス会に来ていただきありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to the Christmas party today!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
メリークリスマス！
Merry Christmas!
なんか召喚の儀みたいになってますけど...
It looks like some kind of summoning ritual...
いやあ、お二人は...
Well, you two...
え、もしかなんですけど、3Dね...
Well, maybe... you recently got your 3D models,
最近なったじゃないですか。そこから...
right? Since then,
先輩のゲストとかってあったり？
have you been a guest for a senpai before?
実は...
Actually...
初めてです！
it's our first time!
イエーイ！
Yay!
初めてでーす！
It's the first time!
ね、二人が元気に動いてる姿こんな間近で見れて...
Man, seeing you two moving so energetically up close like this...
なんか動きが...あれ？
Something about your movements... wait?
だいたい同じ。イエーイ！
They're pretty much the same. Yay!
ちょっと、はしゃいじゃってるんですけど。
Hey, you're getting a bit too excited.
いやでもね、二人を呼んだ理由ちゃんとあります。
But you know, there's a proper reason why I invited you two.
お、何でしょう？
Oh, what is it?
動きが変。
Your movements are weird.
いや確かにね。なんかふとした時にね、なんか二人ちょっと動き似てるって...
Well, that's true. Sometimes we realize our movements are a bit similar...
団長ね、ちょっと、あの、ありがとうございます。
I'm, well, thank you very much.
嬉しい、嬉しい。
I'm happy, so happy.
だけどそうではなく、あの、ま、今日歌った曲...
But that's not it. The song we sang today...
歌ったことあるよね。
You've sung it before, right?
そうなんです、カバーしたことあるよね！
That's right, we've covered it before!
ぜひ、理々華ちゃんの「歌ってみた」も聞いてください。
Please be sure to listen to Ririka-chan's cover version too.
ありがとう！ぜひぜひ！
Thank you! Please do!
でも今回の方がめちゃめちゃめちゃいい感じなんで、そっちをいっぱい聞いて！
But this time was way, way better, so listen to this one a lot!
そしてね、やっぱ奏ちゃんはね、もう団長ReGLOSSの中で一番絡んでる、もう娘。
And you know, Kanade-chan is the one in ReGLOSS I've interacted with most... she's like my daughter.
ママ！ノエルママ！愛してるー！
Mama! Noel-mama! I love you!
呼ばなきゃと思って、呼びました。
I felt like I had to invite you, so here you are.
赤ちゃんだよ。ありがとう。ベイビーノエル。バブーノエル。
I'm a baby. Thank you. Baby Noel. Babu-Noel.
嬉しい、ありがとうね、本当に歌いにも来てくれて。
I'm happy. Thank you so much for coming to sing today.
ちなみにお二人はクリスマスの思い出とかってありますか？
By the way, do you two have any Christmas memories?
はい！ / お、あります！
Yes! / Oh, I have one!
やっぱりクリスマスといえばケーキじゃないですか。
Well, when you think of Christmas, you think of cake, right?
だからクリスマスの終わった翌日に安くなったケーキをいっぱい食べることです。
So my memory is eating lots of cake the day after Christmas when it gets cheaper.
素敵じゃん。大好き。
That's lovely. I love that.
ま、でもね、やっぱ味は変わんないしね。
Well, the taste doesn't change after all.
そう。でも安くなってる。やったね。
Exactly. But it's cheaper. Score!
美味しさ二倍。
Twice the deliciousness.
鷹嶺ちゃんらしき限界を感じますけれども。奏ちゃんは何ですか？
I can feel the 'edge' typical of Takane-chan, but how about you, Kanade-chan?
あ、奏も思い出あります！
Oh, Kanade has a memory too!
ちょっと良い子の皆さんは、ちょっとだけお耳を閉じていただきたいんですけど。
I'd like all the good children out there to cover their ears for a moment.
クリスマスのアレ、幼稚園にいた時の話なんですけど。
It's a story from when I was in kindergarten, about... you know, that thing.
幼稚園のところに来たサンタのコスプレをしたおっさん...
There was this middle-aged guy dressed as Santa who came to the kindergarten...
おっさん？サンタさんでしょ、それ。
Middle-aged guy? You mean Santa Claus, right?
白いカツラの下に黒髪が見えてたことが思い出です。
My memory is seeing his black hair under the white wig.
夢がない！ / 違うよね。
That's so cynical! / It's not like that.
染め忘れちゃったみたい、な。
It was like... he just forgot to dye it.
エクステだったんじゃない？おしゃれサンタさん。
Maybe they were hair extensions? A fashionable Santa.
やっぱ二人はいい思い出をありがとうございます。
Well, thank you both for those... 'great' memories.
でも、これからもまだまだクリスマスライブは続いていくので...
But the Christmas live is going to continue for a while longer...
ちょっとお二人には、ここでお別れになっちゃうんですが。
So I'm afraid it's time to say goodbye to you two for now.
えー、寂しい！やだずっといたい！
Ehh, how lonely! No, I want to stay forever!
でもまだ、ちょっと残っててね。
But wait, stay just a little bit longer.
団長ちょっとお二人にお願いがあります。
I have a small favor to ask you two.
あの後ろの、こちら見えますか？
Can you see this over here, behind us?
デカ！届かない！
It's huge! I can't reach it!
このクリスマスツリーに、飾り付けをお願いしてもいいですか？
Could you help me decorate this Christmas tree?
もちろん！
Of course!
一緒に飾り付けしましょう！
Let's decorate it together!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
わぁー！イエーイ！
Wow! Yay!
飾り付けするぞー！
Let's decorate!
じゃあまずは、奏ちゃんから。
Okay, first up, Kanade-chan.
頑張りまーす！奏ちゃん。
I'll do my best! Kanade-chan.
投げちゃう。
I'm gonna throw it.
おー！できたー！
Oh! You did it!
はい次、鷹嶺。
Okay, next, Takane.
はい、つけまーす。
Okay, I'm putting it on.
どこに付けようかな？
Where should I put it?
じゃあ華麗に、えい！
Then, with flair... hup!
おー！美しい！
Oh! Beautiful!
完璧完璧！ありがとう、お二人。
Perfect, perfect! Thank you both.
引き続き頑張ってくださいね。
Please keep doing your best.
頑張るぞー！イエーイ！
Let's do this! Yay!
全身小悪魔精神 フローラル柑橘香水系
Full-body little devil spirit, floral citrus perfume type
予備もばっちり
Backups are all ready
恋まで発展わっ！
Developing into love, whoa!
大胆 大胆 アタシってハッピー
Bold, bold, I'm so happy
お招き本気のジュナジュナボーイ
Inviting you, my serious Juna Juna boy
豪快 豪快 悩殺ゴースマイル
Exciting, exciting, a killer go-smile
あらまってキュンキュンハニーハニーイェー
Oh my, my heart's fluttering, honey honey yeah
ホロホロで惚れ惚れでバイタル不安ね
Head over heels, totally charmed, my vitals are unstable
空振って本気のジュナジュナボーイ
Swinging and missing, my serious Juna Juna boy
ホロホロで惚れ惚れでバイタル不安ね
Head over heels, totally charmed, my vitals are unstable
あらまってキュンキュンハニーハニーイェー
Oh my, my heart's fluttering, honey honey yeah
全身小悪魔精神性 あなたを完全掌握です
Full-body little devil mentality, I've got you completely under my thumb
盲目ハッピーアンラッキー 真面目な恋とか気にしちゃメン
Blind happy unlucky, I don't care about serious love
全身小悪魔精神性 フローラル柑橘香水系
Full-body little devil mentality, floral citrus perfume scent
よそ見はバッテン 恋まで発展わっ！
Looking away is forbidden, developing into love, whoa!
イジワルしちゃうぞ少女 惚れちゃいな
I'm gonna be mean, little girl, just fall for me
ドキドキ肝心なドライ
Heart-pounding, crucially dry
イジワルしちゃうぞ可愛くね
I'm gonna be mean, in a cute way
付き合ってとかダメダメ独占じゃん
Asking to date? No way, that's just a monopoly
イタズラーニャ！イタズラーニャ！
Itazura-nya! Itazura-nya!
イタズラーニャ！怒らないでね
Itazura-nya! Don't be mad
イタズラーニャ！イタズラーニャ！
Itazura-nya! Itazura-nya!
イタズラーニャ！アタシだけの愛
Itazura-nya! My love alone
毎晩毎晩 未読で反省
Every night, every night, reflecting on unread messages
絡めのムチムチ気分気分が
Entangled, plump feelings, feelings...
大変大変 肌ケアエイジング
Oh boy, oh boy, skin care aging
夜更かしNG ピュアピュアC
Staying up late is a no-no, Pure Pure C
ホロホロで転がしてたまには放っといて
Spinning me around, leave me alone sometimes
欲しがり寂しむ気分気分が
Wanting more, feeling lonely, feelings...
ホロホロで転がしてたまには放っといて
Spinning me around, leave me alone sometimes
ナマコは３度目のスルー
Namako is the third time being ignored
イジワルしちゃうぞ冷めちゃいや
I'm gonna be mean, don't lose interest
ほら眼中外なんてWhy?
Look, why am I out of your sight?
イジワルしちゃうぞ変えちゃいや
I'm gonna be mean, don't change it
でも端正なダイヤイヤ反抗タイム
But neat diamond, no, resistance time
イタズラーニャ！イタズラーニャ！
Itazura-nya! Itazura-nya!
イタズラーニャ！離れないでしょ？
Itazura-nya! You won't leave, right?
イタズラーニャ！イタズラーニャ！
Itazura-nya! Itazura-nya!
イタズラーニャ！アタシだけの愛
Itazura-nya! My love alone
ちょっちょっ可愛くない？
Hey, hey, aren't I cute?
ちょっちょっ答えてよ
Hey, hey, answer me
ちょっちょっ寂しいな
Hey, hey, I'm lonely
ちょっちょっ分からずや
Hey, hey, you stubborn person
ちょっちょっ可愛くない？
Hey, hey, aren't I cute?
ちょっちょっ答えてよ
Hey, hey, answer me
ちょっちょっ寂しいな
Hey, hey, I'm lonely
それじゃあ私もイタズラだ
In that case, I'll be mischievous too
全身小悪魔精神性 あなたを完全掌握です
Full-body little devil mentality, I've got you completely under my thumb
盲目ハッピーアンラッキー 真面目な恋とか気にしちゃメン
Blind happy unlucky, I don't care about serious love
全身小悪魔精神性 フローラル柑橘香水系
Full-body little devil mentality, floral citrus perfume scent
よそ見はバッテン 恋まで発展わっ！
Looking away is forbidden, developing into love, whoa!
イジワルしちゃうぞ少女 惚れちゃいな
I'm gonna be mean, little girl, just fall for me
ドキドキ肝心なドライ
Heart-pounding, crucially dry
イジワルしちゃうぞ可愛くね
I'm gonna be mean, in a cute way
付き合ってとかダメダメ独占じゃん
Asking to date? No way, that's just a monopoly
イタズラーニャ！イタズラーニャ！
Itazura-nya! Itazura-nya!
イタズラーニャ！怒らないでね
Itazura-nya! Don't be mad
イタズラーニャ！イタズラーニャ！
Itazura-nya! Itazura-nya!
イタズラーニャ！アタシだけの愛
Itazura-nya! My love alone
寂しがりなさい
Feel lonely for me
近づいている 冬の足音
The footsteps of winter are approaching
耳を澄ませば 聞こえる鈴の音...
If you listen closely, you can hear the sound of bells...
...聞こえる鈴の音
...hear the sound of bells
寝ぼけた頭に 響く目覚ましを
The alarm clock rings in my sleepy head
手さぐりで止めたあと 雪の気配
After fumbling to stop it, the hint of snow
始まりを告げる すてきな季節が
A wonderful season that heralds the beginning
Happy holidays, happy holidays
What a glorious time of year!
すやすやと眠る 子供達の手に
In the hands of children sleeping soundly
抱かれたテディベアも もう待ちきれない
Even the teddy bear they're holding can't wait any longer
抱かれたテディベアも　もう待ちきれない
Even the teddy bear being hugged can't wait anymore
クリスマスが今年もやって来る
Christmas is coming again this year
悲しかった出来事を　消し去るように
As if to erase the sad events
さあ　パジャマを脱いだら　出かけよう
Come on, once you've taken off your pajamas, let's go out
少しずつ白くなる　街路樹を駆け抜けて
Run through the street trees that are gradually turning white
華やぎ始めた　街は急ぎ足
The town has begun to brighten up, everyone is in a hurry
贈り物決まる頃　黄昏れていく
By the time the gifts are decided, twilight is falling
かじかんだ指を　ママが温めるね
Mom will warm your frozen fingers
Happy holidays, happy holidays
What a glorious time of year
大切なものは　みんなそばにある
Everything important is right by your side
穏やかな毎日が　続くぜいたく
The luxury of peaceful days continuing
クリスマスがもうじきやって来る
Christmas will be here very soon
うれしさをかくせない　犬や猫まで
Even dogs and cats can't hide their joy
もみの木に灯る　明かりをうけて
In the light of the fir tree
いつもよりやさしそうな　パパの目が笑ってる
Dad's eyes, looking kinder than usual, are smiling
クリスマスは誰にでもやって来る
Christmas comes to everyone
もしひとりぼっちでも　淋しがらずに
Even if you're all alone, don't be lonely
心に住むサンタに呼びかけて
Call out to the Santa living in your heart
幼い頃の夢を　思い出してごらんよ
Try to remember your childhood dreams
クリスマスが今年もやって来る
Christmas is coming again this year
悲しかった出来事を　消し去るように
As if to erase the sad events
さあ　パジャマを脱いだら　出かけよう
Come on, once you've taken off your pajamas, let's go out
少しずつ白くなる　街路樹を駆け抜けて
Run through the street trees that are gradually turning white
Happy happy holidays
IN MY DREAM
作詞・作曲：真行寺 恵里
Lyrics & Composition: Eri Shingyoji
Nightmare　あなたは夢に　勝手に入り込んで
Nightmare, you enter my dreams without permission
気が狂いそうなほど　夢中にさせて
Making me so infatuated it feels like I'm going crazy
消えてゆくのに
Even though you fade away
芝生に寝転ぶ彼　まるで別人なの
He's lying on the grass, looking like a completely different person
挑発されたい　刺激的に情熱的にね
I want to be provoked, excitingly and passionately
In My Dream　赤い薔薇の花
In My Dream, red roses
部屋中にいっぱい　敷きつめて
Fill the whole room with them
シルクのベッドで　愛し合おう朝まで
Let's make love on a silk bed until morning
I can't get enough your love
In My Dream　目覚めさせないで
In My Dream, don't wake me up
邪魔はさせない　誰にも
I won't let anyone get in the way
耳元でいつも　エンドレステープのように
Always by my ear, like an endless tape
囁いていて　Love me Forever
Whisper to me, Love me Forever
Day Dream　何度誘っても
Day Dream, no matter how many times I invite you
...としても上の空
...my mind is elsewhere.
分離したカフェオーレは
The separated cafe au lait is...
二人の心みたいに 冷めてる
...cold, just like our hearts.
期待とは裏腹に 後退する気分
Contrary to expectations, I feel like I'm retreating.
触発されたい 野性的に 官能的に
I want to be inspired, wildly and sensually.
In My Dream 空の彼方まで
In My Dream, to the ends of the sky.
エンジン全開で走りながら
Running with the engine at full throttle.
永遠の愛を語ろう 朝まで
Let's talk of eternal love until morning.
I can't get enough your love
I can't get enough of your love.
In My Dream 飾らない涙で
In My Dream, with unadorned tears.
悲しみさえも分かち合おう
Let's share even our sadness.
何処にもないような素晴らしい real love
A wonderful real love like nowhere else.
手に入れるまで I wanna sleep forever
Until I have it, I want to sleep forever.
In My Dream 赤い薔薇の花
In My Dream, red roses.
部屋中にいっぱい敷きつめて
Spread all over the room.
シルクのベッドで愛し合おう 朝まで
Let's make love on a silk bed until morning.
I can't get enough your love
I can't get enough of your love.
In My Dream 目覚めさせないで
In My Dream, don't wake me up.
邪魔はさせない誰にも
I won't let anyone get in the way.
耳元でいつもエンドレス・テープのように
Always in my ear, like an endless tape...
囁いていて
...keep whispering.
In My Dream 空の彼方まで
In My Dream, to the ends of the sky.
エンジン全開で走りながら
Running with the engine at full throttle.
永遠の愛を語ろう 朝まで
Let's talk of eternal love until morning.
I can't get enough your love
I can't get enough of your love.
In My Dream 飾らない涙で
In My Dream, with unadorned tears.
悲しみさえも分かち合おう
Let's share even our sadness.
何処にもないような素晴らしい real love
A wonderful real love like nowhere else.
手に入れるまで I wanna sleep forever
Until I have it, I want to sleep forever.
Starduster / 作詞・作曲：ジミーサムP
Starduster / Lyrics & Composition: JimmyThumb-P
誰より大切な君に
To you, who are more precious than anyone,
愛されないことを恐れて
fearful of not being loved,
一万年先の星まで
to a star ten thousand years away,
ひとっ跳びで逃げた
I fled in a single bound.
そっと瞼を開けてみる
I gently try to open my eyes.
目の前は黒い空の海
Before me is the black sea of the sky.
一億年先の地平まで
To the horizon a hundred million years away,
流れてゆくんだ
it flows on.
吸い込んだ
I inhaled...
真空の温度で
...the temperature of the vacuum.
感覚が 凍りつく前にもう
Before my senses freeze over,
この体の
this body's...
...からな
...I know that.
一身分つ 体の分の一の
A fraction of one body's worth of
愛を
Love...
愛を 今すぐ
Love, right now
愛を 私に
Love, to me
愛を どうか
Love, please
愛を 愛を 愛を 愛を
Love, love, love, love...
光射さぬ星の上で
On a star where light does not reach
暗闇に呑まれないように
So as not to be swallowed by the darkness
一万年先の夕焼けを
A sunset ten thousand years away
ひとりで見てた
I was watching alone
きっとこの宇宙の塵と
I'm sure, with the dust of this universe
ずっと漂うだけなんだろう
I'll probably just drift forever
そうやって消えて無くなる前に
Before I vanish like that
どうか どうか...
Please, please...
愛を 今すぐ
Love, right now
愛を 私に
Love, to me
愛を どうか
Love, please
愛を 愛を 愛を 愛を
Love, love, love, love...
愛を...
Love...
チキンライス
作詞：松本人志　作曲：槇原敬之
Chicken Rice
Lyrics: Hitoshi Matsumoto / Composition: Noriyuki Makihara
親孝行って何？って考える
I wonder what it means to be a good child
でもそれを考えようとすることがもう
親孝行なのかもしれない
But the act of trying to think about it might already be it
子供の頃たまに家族で外食
When I was a kid, we'd occasionally eat out as a family
いつも頼んでいたのはチキンライス
What I always ordered was chicken rice
豪華なもの頼めば二度と連れては
もらえないような気がして
I felt like if I ordered something fancy,
I'd never be taken out again
親に気を使っていたあんな気持ち
That feeling of being considerate of my parents
今の子供に理解できるかな
I wonder if kids today can understand that
今日はクリスマス
Today is Christmas
街はにぎやか お祭り騒ぎ
The city is lively, a festive bustle
七面鳥はやっぱり照れる
Turkey is still a bit embarrassing
俺はまだまだチキンライスでいいや
I'm still fine with just chicken rice
貧乏って何？って考える
I wonder what it means to be poor
へこんだとこ へこんだ分だけ笑いで
By the amount things were lacking,
満たすしかなかったあの頃
I had no choice but to fill it with laughter back then
昔話を語り出すと決まって
Whenever I start telling stories about the past,
貧乏自慢ですかと言う顔するやつ
people give me that look like, "Are you boasting about being poor?"
でもあれだけ貧乏だったんだ
But we really were that poor,
せめて自慢くらいさせてくれ
so at least let me boast about it a little.
最後は笑いに変えるから
Because I'll turn it into a laugh in the end.
今の子供に嫌がられるかな
I wonder if kids today would find it annoying.
今日はクリスマス
Today is Christmas.
街は賑やか お祭り騒ぎ
The city is bustling with festive excitement.
七面鳥はやっぱり照れる
Turkey still makes me feel a bit self-conscious.
俺はまだまだチキンライスでいいや
I'm still happy with just chicken rice.
今ならなんだって注文できる
Nowadays, I can order whatever I want.
親の顔色を気にしてチキンライス
But I used to order chicken rice, worrying about my parents.
頼む事なんて今はしなくても良い
I don't have to worry about what to order now.
好きなもの何でも頼めるさ
I can order anything I like.
酸っぱい湯気が立ち込める向こう
Beyond the sour steam rising up,
見えた笑顔が今も忘れられない
I still can't forget the smile I saw back then.
今日はクリスマス
Today is Christmas.
街は賑やか お祭り騒ぎ
The city is bustling with festive excitement.
でかいケーキ持ってこい
Bring on a giant cake!
でもまあ全部食べ切れるサイズのもな
But well, let it be a size I can actually finish.
赤坂プリンス押さえとけ
Book a room at the Akasaka Prince.
スイートとまでは言わないが
I won't go so far as to say a suite.
七面鳥もってこい これが七面鳥か
Bring on the turkey! So this is what it's like...
思ってたよりデカいな
It's bigger than I thought.
やっぱり俺はチキンライスがいいや
Actually, I think I'd rather have chicken rice.
よし！あとは、ツリーをライトアップさせたら完成だ！
Alright! All that's left is to light up the tree, and we're done!
ということで、大三、よろしくね！パワーだよ！
So, Daisan, I'm counting on you! Use your power!
それじゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
大三、発電！行け！
Daisan, generate power! Go!
行け！頑張れ、走れ、走れ！行け、行け、行け、行け、頑張れ！
Go! Good luck, run, run! Go, go, go, go, you can do it!
めっちゃ頑張ってる！頑張ってる！回し車を...
He's working so hard! He's working hard on the wheel...
お、すごいすごい！発電できてる！
Oh, amazing! You're generating power!
行け行け！ファイト、ファイト！こっちか...
Go, go! Fight, fight! This way...
団長もね、ちょっとエアでやるよ！やるやる！行けるよ！
I'll do some air-running too! I'll do it! You can do it!
ファイト、ファイト！大三、大三、頑張れ！大三！
Fight, fight! Daisan, Daisan, you can do it! Daisan!
あ、疲れてる...大三、ほっぺた膨らませながら...あ、息が...息がゼーゼー言ってる...
Ah, he's tired... Daisan, your cheeks are puffed out... Oh, his breath... He's gasping for air...
ちょっと、でも、大三...あ、ライト消えちゃった！ああ、どうしよう！
Wait, but Daisan... Oh, the lights went out! Oh no, what should we do!
でも、あれなの。それさ、ノエちゃんがその滑車回したいところだけど、ちょっとノエちゃんの体重じゃ、あの、壊れちゃうんで...
But, here's the thing. I'd love to spin that wheel myself, but with my weight, well, it would break...
大三が頼みなんだ！ツリー完成目指して、走るんだ！頑張れ！
Daisan, you're our only hope! Run so we can finish the tree! Good luck!
行け、頑張れ、頑張れ！頑張ってる、頑張ってる！
Go, good luck, good luck! He's doing it, he's doing it!
行け、行け、頑張れ、頑張れ！あー頑張ってる！いいよ、いいよ！
Go, go, good luck, good luck! Ah, he's working so hard! Good, good!
行け、行け！お、回ってる、回ってる！お、待って待って！
Go, go! Oh, it's spinning, it's spinning! Oh, wait, wait!
ツリー、あ、光り始めてる！すごいよ！
The tree, oh, it's starting to light up! This is amazing!
あ、いい、来てる来てる！光った光った！頑張れ、あともうちょっと！行け行け行け行け！
Ah, yes, it's coming, it's coming! It lit up, it lit up! Good luck, just a little more! Go, go, go, go!
あーっ！あーっ！
Ah! Ah!
待て、あともうちょっと！
Wait, just a little bit more!
星が点滅すれば成功なんだけど...
If the star flashes, it'll be a success, but...
あー！きたー！
Ah! It's here!
わーい！
Yay!
星が光ったー！
The star lit up!
ダイサン、ありがとう！
Daisan, thank you!
（ゼーハー、ゼーハー...）
(Panting...)
喜んで、いえーい！
I'm so happy, yay!
ツリーのライトアップできました！
The tree light-up is complete!
やったー！共同作業だー！
We did it! It was a joint effort!
はぁー、本当にエモいだよ。
Haa, this is truly emotional.
いや、これクリスマスもう完璧なんじゃないのか？
I mean, isn't this Christmas already perfect?
ね？あれ？ちょっと待って...
Right? Oh? Wait a second...
もししかして、雪が...
Is that... snow...?
あーっ！やっぱ降ってる！今ポツッて...
Ah! It really is falling! Just now, a drop...
雪がね、降ってきましたね！
The snow has started falling, hasn't it!
ダイサン、やるかい？いえーい！
Daisan, you doing this? Yay!
ホワイトクリスマスだ！
It's a White Christmas!
最高のクリスマス！
The best Christmas ever!
ちょっと祝っちゃいますか！
Let's celebrate a little!
祝うために、歌いますか！
To celebrate, shall we sing?!
では、歌おうー！
Alright, let's sing!
わーい、雪だー！
Yay, it's snow!
Snow halation
作詞：畑 亜貴　作曲：山田 高弘
Lyrics: Aki Hata  Composition: Takahiro Yamada
不思議だね いまの気持ち
It's strange, my feelings right now
空から降ってきたみたい
Like they fell from the sky
特別な季節の色が
The colors of this special season...
ときめきを見せるよ
...show me a heart-throb
初めて出会った時から
From the moment we first met...
予感に騒ぐ心のMelody
...my heart's melody has been racing
とめられない止まらない なぜ
I can't stop it, it won't stop, why?
届け切なさには
Send it out, for this painful feeling...
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
Shall we name it "Snow halation"?
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap...
待てずに悔しいけど
It's frustrating that I can't wait,
好きって純情
but my love is pure
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, it's no use hesitating
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I agree with the courage to dive in
まもなくStart!!
Starting soon!!
音もなく気配もなく
Without a sound or a sign...
静かに運命は変わる
...fate quietly changes
これからの未来に胸の
Looking toward the future, the throbbing...
鼓動が早くなる
...in my chest is getting faster
例えば困った時には
For example, when you're in trouble...
すぐ駆けつけて抱きしめたくて
I want to rush to you and hold you
どこにいてもどこでも Fly high
Wherever you are, everywhere, Fly high
急いでいつのまにか
Hurry, before I knew it...
大きくなりすぎた “True emotion”
...it grew too big, my "True emotion"
夢だけみてる様じゃ つらいよ
If I'm just dreaming, it's painful
恋人は君って言いたい
I want to say you are my lover
優しい目がとまどってる イヤだよ
Your kind eyes are bewildered, I hate it
このまま一気に愛情
Just like this, all at once...
あずけて Please!!
...please entrust me with your love!!
届けて切なさには
Send it out, for this painful feeling...
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
Shall we name it "Snow halation"?
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap...
待てずに悔しいけど
It's frustrating that I can't wait,
好きって純情
but my love is pure
微熱の中 ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, it's no use hesitating
飛び込む勇気に賛成 まもなくStart!!
I'm for the courage to dive in. It's about to start!!
いや、今日は本当に最高のクリスマス・イブだー！
Man, today is truly the best Christmas Eve ever!
いや、あとは、本物のサンタさんが来るの待つのみ！と、
Now, all that's left is to wait for the real Santa Claus! And,
その前にですね、ま、サンタさんはまだ来ないんですけど、
Before that, well, Santa hasn't arrived yet, but
なんとスペシャルな方からメッセージが届いてるらしいです！
I've heard that a message has arrived from someone special!
えー、こちらのモニターをご覧ください。ずん。
Um, please take a look at this monitor. Ta-da.
ドキドキ、ドキドキ。
*Heart pounding, heart pounding.*
ばんちゃお！メリークリスマス！
Banchao! Merry Christmas!
わあ、メリークリスマス！
Wow, Merry Christmas!
皆さんこんにちは、伊織もえです。
Hello everyone, I'm Iori Moe.
もえちゃんだ。
It's Moe-chan.
本日はこんな素敵なクリスマスライブに呼んでいただいてありがとうございます。
Thank you for inviting me to such a wonderful Christmas live today.
こちらこそ！
The pleasure is mine!
私もクリスマスがすっごく好きで、おうちにツリーを飾ったり、ずっとクリスマスのBGMを聴いたりしています。
I also love Christmas very much, so I decorate the tree at home and listen to Christmas BGM all the time.
わかる！
I totally get that!
そして、もえちゃん見てほしい。今日、コスプレ用意してきました。
And, I want you to see this. Today, I've prepared a cosplay.
ほ、ホントでしょ？
R-Really?
新衣装でノエルちゃんが着ていた、シスター×黒騎士が本当に可愛くって、
The sister x black knight outfit Noel-chan wore in her new costume was so cute,
あと、ここがショートカットになってるノエルちゃんもすごく新鮮で、もう心に刺さったので、
and the short-haired Noel-chan was also very fresh, it really struck my heart,
今回このためにコスプレを用意してきました。
so I prepared a cosplay for this occasion.
ありがとう！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
今日は皆さんとノエルちゃん、クリスマスライブでとっても楽しんでると思うんですけど、
I think everyone and Noel-chan are having a great time at the Christmas live today,
もう一つ、大事な日を忘れてませんか？
but aren't you forgetting one more important day?
大事な日？
An important day?
そう、それはノエルちゃん、
That's right, it's Noel-chan,
あなたの、お誕生日です！
your birthday!
え、もえちゃん！
Eh, Moe-chan!
ノエルちゃん、改めてお誕生日おめでとうございます！
Noel-chan, once again, Happy Birthday!
あ、ありがとうございます！
Ah, thank you very much!
いつもノエルちゃんの可愛い奮闘してる姿を見ているんですけど、やっぱりお誕生日はお祝いしたいなと思って駆けつけました。
I'm always watching Noel-chan's cute, struggling efforts, so I rushed here thinking I'd definitely like to celebrate your birthday.
いつもね、これからも活動応援しております。
As always, I'll continue to support your activities.
誕生日、嬉しいですぅ。
Birthday, I'm so happy.
以上、伊織もえでした。改めてノエルちゃんお誕生日おめでとう！バイバイ！
That's all from Iori Moe. Happy Birthday again, Noel-chan! Bye-bye!
行かないで、もえちゃん、あー、もえちゃん、バイバイ、もえちゃん。
Don't go, Moe-chan, ah, Moe-chan, bye-bye, Moe-chan.
可愛かった。もえちゃん、あの団長のね、あのシスター衣装のコスプレをしてくれて、
She was so cute. Moe-chan cosplayed as the sister outfit I wore,
まさかの、なんかまさかの、なんかサプライズみたいな感じだったんですけど、
it was such an unexpected surprise,
え、でも、なんかありがとうございますなんですけど、クリスマス？ お誕生日？
Eh, but, well, thank you very much, but Christmas? Birthday?
あ、でも、お誕生日なら、とりあえず、アレがあるってことかな？
Ah, but, if it's my birthday, I guess that means there's that?
ということで、今年も、あります！ こちら、ダダン！
So, we have it again this year! Here it is, ta-da!
白銀ノエル、誕生日記念2024！ わあ、出てきた！
Shirogane Noel Birthday Celebration 2024! Wow, it's here!
はい、詳細を見ていきましょう。まずは、こちら！
Yes, let's take a look at the details. First, this one!
ノエサンタがお届け！アクリルジオラマスタンド！ ということで、あのイラストレーターさんは、MyungYiさんに仕立てていただきました。
"Noe-Santa Delivers! Acrylic Diorama Stand!" The illustrator for this is MyungYi-san.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
いや、これ、可愛い。あのノエサンタですよね。多分、団員さんにプレゼントを持って、行こうとしてるところなんじゃないかなって感じなんですけど、
Man, this is cute. It's Noe-Santa. I think she's about to go deliver presents to the guild members,
めっちゃ可愛い。
really cute.
いや、本物のサンタはもしかして、ノエちゃんだったのかなと思いつつ、こちらね、おうちにぜひぜひ飾ってみてください。
While thinking that the real Santa might have been Noe-chan after all, please do display this at home.
そして、次はこちら！
And, next is this one!
ノエちゃんランダム缶バッジということでね、いっぱいあるんですけど、団長ね、缶バッジってあんまり出したことないよね。
It's the "Noe-chan Random Button Badges," there are a lot of them, but I haven't really released button badges that much, have I?
でもね、いろいろ憧れてたんです。他のホロメンとかがさ、こういう誕生日とか周年に缶バッジ出して、
But I've been admiring it for a long time. Seeing other Holomem releasing button badges for birthdays and anniversaries,
それを団員さんとかが、集めてくれると… あ、なんかぐちゃぐちゃになっちゃった、ま、そのリスナーさんが集めて、
and having the fans collect them... ah, I'm getting confused, well, having listeners collect them and,
痛バとか作ってるの見て、団員さんもぜひ、ノエちゃんの痛バとか作ってほしいなっていう、
seeing them make "ita-bags" (fandom bags), I really want the guild members to make Noe-chan ita-bags too.
あの、団員さんはあれだよ、他の女の子の缶バッジ買っちゃダメだからね。ちょっと言葉間違えちゃいました。
But guild members, you're not allowed to buy button badges of other girls, okay? I worded that a bit wrong.
こちらはイラストレーター、なだない先生に描いていただきました。
These were illustrated by Nadanai-sensei.
色々な衣装のノエちゃん、ぜひぜひ、あの単品でも売ってますので、集めてください。
Please collect these Noe-chans in various outfits, they're also sold individually.
ま、どれが来ても嬉しいし、被っちゃっても痛バックにすればオッケー！ そして、次はこちら！
Well, whichever one you get will make me happy, and even if you get duplicates, it's okay if you use them for an ita-bag! And, next is this one!
ノエサンタぬいぐるみキーホルダー！ ということで、ノエサンタのぬいぐるみキーホルダーです。
"Noe-Santa Plushie Keychain!" So, it's a Noe-Santa plushie keychain.
先ほどご紹介した、はい、アクリルジオラマスタンドの...
The Acrylic Diorama Stand I introduced earlier...
...衣装と同じノエルサンタとなっております。
...comes in the same Noel Santa outfit.
可愛いでしょう、こちらオリジナル衣装となっていますので...
Isn't it cute? It's an original outfit...
...ぜひ今日のね、記念というか、お祝い？思い出だね。
...so please, as a commemorative item, or a celebration? A memory, right.
ぜひぜひ、あの、飾ってください。よろしくお願いします。
Please, please display it. Thank you.
ま、思い出といったらこちらも欲しいよね。
Well, speaking of memories, you'd want this too.
ということで、次はこちら！
So, next is this!
はい！「団員さんとの想い出オーナメントキーホルダー」ということで...
Yes! The "Memories with Dan-in Ornament Key Holder"...
...あのこちらですね、団員さん、クリスマスツリーにポポポポーンって、
...this is, Dan-ins, like 'pop pop pop' on your Christmas tree...
...オーナメント飾ったと思うんですけど、
...I think you've decorated it with ornaments,
こちら、はい、えーちょっとグッズにしちゃいました。
but here, yes, I made it into a piece of merch.
しかも団員さんもね、一生懸命あの回し車回してくれて、
And the Dan-ins too, they were spinning the hamster wheel so hard,
参加してくれてたので、はい。
and participating, yes.
でも、団長ね、ちょっと忘れてたことが...
But, I (Danchou) forgot something...
こちら！ドゥン！
This! Dun!
あの、みんなに投げるの忘れてました。
Um, I forgot to throw it to everyone.
ということで、やっぱ、なんか小ネタがあったほうがいいかなということで、
So, I thought it'd be better to have a little skit or something,
「想い出」と付いたら、やっぱ団員さんのもとに届けなきゃいけない。
since it says "Memories", I have to deliver it to the Dan-ins.
だから団長、ここでさ「わーい」って投げるから、団員さんキャッチしてください！
So I'll throw it like "Wheee!", so Dan-ins, please catch it!
で、そのキャッチしたやつが、まあなんか、想い出として団員さんのキーホルダーとなって、
And that caught item, well, will become a Dan-in key holder as a memory,
こちらも付いてくる、みたいな「てい」でいきましょう。「てい」って言っちゃダメか。
let's go with that "premise". I shouldn't have said "premise".
まあ、いくよ！受け取ってね！
Well, here I go! Please catch it!
えいやぁーー！！
Eiyaaa!!
あぁーーー！！届いたぁーー！！
Aaaah!! It reached you!!
やばい、なんかハムスターたちが「俺のだ俺のだ俺のだ」ってなんか...
Oh no, the hamsters are like "It's mine, it's mine, it's mine"...
...すごいね、競争していたんですけど。
...they were competing quite a lot.
あの、ご購、ご購入いただければ、ご購入いただければね、
Um, if you pur- purchase it, if you purchase it,
皆さんのもとに届くので、喧嘩しないでねっていうことで。
it will be delivered to you, so please don't fight.
えー、次も参ります。次はこちら！
Next, please. Next is this!
はい！まあ、ノエルちゃんといえばASMRかなと思い、
Yes! Well, when you think of Noel-chan, you think of ASMR, so...
ASMRボイス「ノエルサンタからのお便り」も、ちょっとこちら、はい、ご用意させていただきました。
...I've prepared the ASMR voice "A Message from Noel Santa" here.
まあ、どんな内容なのかは、聞いてのお楽しみでございます。ぜひぜひ聞いてくれると嬉しいです。
Well, what the content is like is a surprise for when you listen. I'd be happy if you'd listen to it.
そして、次はこちら！
And, next is this!
はい、フルセット購入特典ということで、今回もフルセット購入特典あります。
Yes, a Full Set Purchase Bonus. We have one this time too.
えー、こちらですね、数量限定と数量限定じゃないバージョンがあるんですけど、
Um, for this, there's a limited quantity and a non-limited version,
何が違うかというと、数量限定は直筆サインを書かせていただきます。
and the difference is that the limited version will have my handwritten signature.
で、数量限定じゃない方は箔押し複製となっておりますので、
The non-limited version will have a foil-stamped reproduction,
ぜひ直筆、あの、頑張って書くので、ゲットしてみてください。よろしくお願いします。
so please try to get the handwritten one, I'll work hard writing them. Thank you.
ま、団長、いやノエルちゃん的には、まあクリスマスね、
Well, for me (Danchou), or Noel-chan, well, it's Christmas,
一応今日クリスマス・イブっちゅうことなんで、
it's Christmas Eve today, technically,
あの、団員さんたちもね、自分への日頃のご褒備？プレゼントとして、
so Dan-ins, as a reward for yourself? As a present,
このグッズ、あの、お手にとってみてくれると嬉しいんじゃないかな、ハッピーなんじゃないかな。
I'd be happy, it'd be happy if you could get this merch.
あ、ノエルちゃんも嬉しいって、よろしくお願いします。
Oh, Noel-chan would be happy too. Thank you.
はい、そして改めて、フルセットはこちらとなります。はい！
Yes, and once again, here is the full set. Yes!
ということで、はい。いや、すごい、たくさん思い出セットみたいになっておりますので、
So, yes. Wow, it's like a big "memories set",
ぜひクリスマスプレゼントにゲットしてみてください。団長も欲しいよ。
so please get it as a Christmas present. I want one too!
そして、えー、プレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、
And, as a bonus for the premium goods full set,
今年の9月から発売されたホロライブ・オフィシャル・カード・ゲームで使用できるカードが、
a card that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME, which was released this September,
なんと1枚つきます！いやこれ嬉しい！ノエルちゃんも欲しい！
will actually be included! Wow, I'm so happy! Noel-chan wants it too!
えー、カードはホロライブプロダクション・オフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となります。
Um, the card is only for those who purchased from the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP.
特典につくのは、推しをアピールできるキーカード「推しホロメンカード」です。
What's included as a bonus is a "Oshi Holomen Card", a key card to show off your oshi.
カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページにてご確認ください。
Please check the website for card details and how to play.
カードは日本語版のみとなります。
The card will only be available in Japanese.
この配信の後に、カート・オープンです。
The cart will open after this stream.
あの、数量限定もあるので、ぜひ欲しいなって思ってる人はお早めにゲットしてみてください。
There's a limited quantity too, so those who want it, please try to get it early.
そして、この後22時20分から、メン限があります！嬉しいね。
And, from 22:20 after this, there will be a members-only stream! I'm so happy.
ちょっとね、まだまだあのノエルちゃんと一緒にいたいなっていう団員さん、いっぱいいると思うので、
I think there are many Dan-ins who want to stay with Noel-chan a bit longer,
ぜひね、メンバー登録をして待っててください。
so please join the membership and wait for it.
今回はですね、ま、2曲を歌おうかなと思っております。
This time, well, I'm thinking of singing two songs.
可愛い...
Cute...
衣装もちょっと、スクショタイムとか設けて...
I'll set up some screenshot time for this outfit too...
うぉ！いっぱい撮ってもらおうかなって思うので、ぜひよろしくお願いします！
Whoa! I hope you take lots of pictures, so please do!
ということで、今日はクリスマスなのか、お誕生日なのか、もう、なんかわけがわかんなくなって...
So, I'm not sure if today is Christmas or my birthday, I'm getting confused...
ちょっと、息も切れてきてしまったんで、結局どっちなんだ？
I'm a bit out of breath, but which one is it after all?
え、待って、もう、頭がわかんなくな、うわぁー！わかんなくなってきた！うわぁー！
Wait, my head is... Whoa! I'm getting confused! Whoa!
どっちだー！
Which is it!?
ふぁ〜。うわぁ、誕生日、クリスマス...
Yawn... Whoa, birthday, Christmas...
え？
Eh?
あれれ？ここは？あれ？
Huh? Where am I? Wait?
あれ？さっきまで...待って。あ、
Wait, until just now... Hold on. Oh,
カレンダーある！
There's a calendar!
えっと、あ、2024年の、あれ、11月の...あれれ？
Let's see, ah, 2024... wait, November... huh?
11月24日に丸がついて、あれ、ハートになってる！
There's a circle on November 24th... wait, it's a heart!
ってことは、今日はクリスマスじゃないの？あれ？
So, today isn't Christmas? Huh?
ってことは、今までの全部、夢だったってこと？あ！
Does that mean everything until now was a dream? Ah!
そっか！今日はクリスマス・イブの1ヶ月前の、誕生日なんだんだな！
Right! Today is my birthday, one month before Christmas Eve!
そう、よくね、あの、クリスマス・イブの1ヶ月前が団長の誕生日だよとか言ってるから、ごっちゃになってたのか！
That's right, I often say my birthday is a month before Christmas Eve, so I must have gotten confused!
うわぁ、ちょっと、あの、うっかりしてたな。
Whoa, I was a bit careless.
までも、眠いからもう1回寝るか。
Well, I'm sleepy, so I'll go back to sleep.
ま、ちょっと夢の中でまた生誕祝い、おやすみ〜。
Well, back to the birthday celebration in my dreams... goodnight~
ours
作詞・作曲：古川本舗 編曲：古川本舗・和音正人
Lyrics/Composition: Furukawa Honpo / Arrangement: Furukawa Honpo, Masato Kazune
今日はこのまま さよならじゃないよ。
Today won't end with a goodbye just like this.
手をとってくれたなら
If you would take my hand
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
On a night where even secrets seem to fall asleep
君を連れていくよ。
I will take you away.
それは例えば、遠く離れていたって
Even if, for example, we were far apart
手を繋いでいられるような
So that we can keep holding hands
奇跡のような話をしよう！
Let's talk about something like a miracle!
窓は開けておいて。
Leave the window open.
今日までを思い出して
Looking back on everything until today
一つ、一つ並べたら
If I line them up one by one
明日の雨が気になり出して
I start to worry about tomorrow's rain
どうも眠れないみたいだ。
And it seems I can't sleep.
変わりたくないことや、
Things I don't want to change,
変わらなきゃいけないことも
And things that must change
少し忘れたまま
While forgetting them just a little
窓の外を眺めていたんだ。
I was gazing out the window.
あぁ、雨が降り出すその前に
Ah, before the rain starts to fall
君のところまで
To where you are
行けるような気がして、
I feel like I can go,
目を閉じてみたんだ
So I tried closing my eyes
そして、このまま遠くへと行こう。
And let's go far away just like this.
手をとってくれるかな。
Will you take my hand?
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
A night where even secrets seem to fall asleep
君と泳いでいくよ。
I will swim through it with you.
街の明かりが消える度に笑って
Smiling every time the city lights go out
路地裏で抱き合おう。
Let's embrace in the back alley.
馬鹿みたいな話をしよう！
Let's talk about something silly!
窓は開けておいて。
Leave the window open.
聞こえる？
Can you hear it?
愛しいことや、無くせないものを
Precious things, and things I can't lose
教えてくれたのは今日みたいな
What taught me those was a night like today
夜を重ねて織り上げてきた
Woven together by piling up nights
私たちに響く音
The sound that resonates within us
夜が来るたびに心が躍ってしまうのは、
The reason my heart dances every time night comes,
また一つ。
Again, one...
And another...
重なっていくから
Because they keep piling up
目を閉じてみたんだ。
So I tried closing my eyes.
今夜、私たちだけで眠ろう。
Tonight, let's sleep just the two of us.
誰にも言わないで。
Don't tell anyone.
君が眠りにつくその少し前に
Just a little before you fall asleep
...に
...in
名前を呼んで
Call my name
叶わない願いに胸は痛んで
My heart aches with a wish that won't come true
俯いてしまうけど、
I end up looking down, but...
誰もいない街へ誘いに行くから！
I'll come to invite you to a town with no one else!
今日はこのままさよならじゃないよ。
Today isn't just going to end with a goodbye.
手をとってくれたなら
If you would take my hand
秘密を眠りにつくような夜に
On a night where secrets fall asleep
君を連れていくよ。
I'll take you away.
それは例えば遠く離れてたって
Even if, for example, we were far apart
手を繋いでいられるような
As if we could stay holding hands
奇跡のような話をしよう。
Let's talk of something like a miracle.
窓は開けておいて
Keep the window open
聞こえる？
Can you hear it?
愛しいことやなくせないものを
Dear things and things that can't be lost
教えてくれたのは今日みたいな
What taught me that was a night like today
夜を重ねて織り上げてきた
Woven together through many nights
私たちに響く音、
The sound that resonates within us,
響く言葉。
The words that resonate.
見てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for watching!
これからも一緒に誕生日お祝いしてくれるとノエサンタは幸せ太郎です。
Noe-Santa will be extremely happy if you continue to celebrate my birthday with me.
団員さん...ラブち...
Order members... Love you...
メン限アフターライブも見てね！
Check out the members-only after-party live too!